Excuse me, sir. Quick question for you, man. Is this
your G-Wagon? It is. And what do you do for
living out in Dallas to be able to afford
a G-Wagon? I have pursued my career in finance.
The money is in the money business. I had the
blessing to be a former CEO of 7-Eleven. I also
was former chairman and CEO of Blockbuster. So
you were the CEO of 7-Eleven and Blockbuster?
I was the CEO of 7-Eleven and Blockbuster,
yeah. That's incredible. What has been the most amount
of money that you've ever made in a
single year? $16.7 million. $16.7 million. And what happened
that year that you were able to
make over $16 million? American Airlines filed bankruptcy.
Have you ever been broke before? Absolutely. At 29,
I moved back home. I didn't have a phone,
a checking account, and dead broke. And when you
hit rock bottom, there's only one place to go,
and that's up. What has been the most amount
of money that you've ever made in a single year?
Highland Park in Dallas, Texas is the number six
wealthiest city in all of the United States. And
today, we're going to be going
all over Highland Park, asking multi-millionaires,
how they became wealthy, and how you
can start your path to becoming financially free
going into 2024. And with that being
said, let's get this video on the way.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career
in? I pursued my career in finance. The money
is in the money business. Did you go to
college? I went to junior college, but college is not
necessary. College is not necessary? No, no. You get
a school of life. What has been the most
amount of money that you've ever made in a
single year? $16.7 million. And what has been the most
amount of money that you've ever made in
a single year? $650,000 in one year. $650,000. And
that's more than 99% of people will ever make
in a single year. What's the best financial advice
that you've ever received throughout your career?
Well, rich people hire people and poor people
don't. You got to create scale and create leverage.
You got to create that leverage. A lot of times,
people work in isolation, and they're stuck by
their own understanding. Now, I'll ask you a
question, right? You have real dreams. Yes, sir.
They're a shortcut to them. There's no shortcut.
Yes, it is. Yeah. Shortcut is mentorship.
Now, you minimize mistakes. You show them,
turn care, got a straight path forward. In life,
you need a mentor. You don't know where to find
a mentor, and here, she don't know where to find
you. Wow. You live and die, and now they'll find
your dreams. You became a millionaire, but have you
ever been broke before? I was real broke. I
was so broke, I couldn't afford a free stamp.
But see, you can fix broke, you can't fix poverty.
Poverty is a mindset. A lot of folks say, I
was broke, but I wasn't poor. You can always fix
broke, but you can't fix poverty. How old are you
now? I'm 57. What is the best advice that you
would tell to your younger self? You got a moment.
Yes, sir. Okay. I'm going to show you something, right?
Yes, sir. Now, this strip here is from 1 to
100. Now, the average female lives at age 81. Average
male at age 75. So, I'm going to put my finger
here on 75, and I'm going to tear it. I will
probably never see this part of life. If I do,
it would be a blessing, but if I don't, it's not
going to be examinatory. I can't dunk a basketball
then. It's the same quality of life, all right?
Now, I look real young. You may think I'm about
25, but I'm really about 57. So, I put my thumb
here on 57.
And I'm going to tear it. And see, this is gone.
So, this part of the ribbon here is all I got
left. And maybe your ribbon is a little longer,
but you can have one bad sickness, and the quality
of the ribbon ain't the same. What you got left
is what you got left. Live East is a life in
miniature. Live it on steroids and wake up with gratitude.
Thank God I got today is a vote of God
saying this is for you. Live it like you dream
it. My guy made over $700,000 in a single year,
but he just broke down some of the absolute
most important things in the world. So, I'm going to
show you what I got left. I'm going to show you
what I got left. I'm going to show you what I got
left. I'm going to show you what I got left.
I'm going to show you what I got left. So, you're
going to get a real life advice. I'm going to
show you the most unreal life advice that I've ever
seen. Think of your life as like one year, as
like an inch off that measuring tape. Our life on this
earth is limited. It's up to us to make the most
out of the time that we have here. Shout out to
him, man. Dallas is unreal. Let's go get this
next one. What industry did you decide to pursue a
career in? The eyeglass and hearing aid industry. What's
the most amount of money that you ever made
in a single year? $16.7 million. $16.7 million. And
what happened that year that you were able to
make over $16 million? American Airlines
filed bankruptcy. The American Airlines employees, as
you can imagine, aircraft mechanics, baggage
handlers, pilots, they work in an environment
that puts them at risk for hearing loss. And
they had a really generous benefit that would buy them
the best in hearing help and hearing aids,
hearing instruments. And so, when American Airlines filed
bankruptcy, 13,000 local employees panicked and thought,
I had better go use my health insurance
while I still have it. Prior to that, the most
money we had ever made in a year was about $1.5
million. So, this was quite a blessing for
us. We were not wealthy people until this happened.
You literally went from $1 to $16 million
in one year. A lot of business owners,
they struggle to scale and grow. How can someone go
from a $1 to $10 million business? What is the
biggest difference that separates those businesses apart?
Here's the thing. Sometimes people, for the
first time, they start making a little money,
right? They have a first little taste of success
and they get scared thinking, oh, well, I don't
want to lose what I've made. So, don't go there.
Say, okay, well, look, I'm going to continue to
be aggressive. I'm going to continue to take this.
I'm going to take what I've earned here, what
I've made through hard work. Don't be afraid to get
aggressive with it. Spend it. It takes a lot of time.
It takes a lot of time. It takes a lot of
money to make money, right? So, go out there
and buy that house. Buy that second property. Buy the
investment property. Don't be scared to lose what you
finally made. Go reinvest it. How old are you
now? 43. 43. And how old were you when you
became a millionaire? 30. 30 years old. For a young 20-year-old
kid watching this right now, if you could leave
them with a couple last sound bites, give them a
couple last pieces of advice on what it really
takes. Make God a part of your life. And that
may scare some people away. I'm sorry if
it does, but that's the only answer I know.
And that is to seek God in all that you
do, right? And if that's a little heavy for you
in the beginning, then take baby steps.
But have a spiritual aspect to your life.
How important has that faith been
to the success of your business?
Without my faith, without God blessing all that
I've done, there would be no success, right? Number
one. And number two, you need God for
those times where everything ain't okay. Because in business,
in life, very often things are not going to be
okay. They're going to be tough. And if you don't
have somebody or something bigger than yourself to fall
back on, then you're not going to make it.
My guy's business made over $16 million in
a single year because he took advantage of an
opportunity that came up in the market. But
my number one takeaway from that interview was that
he put faith and God first above everything else, and
all the success was added to him. At the end
of the day, man, without God, none of this
is possible. So shout out to him. Gave an amazing
interview. Let's go get this next one. All right, you
guys, my man just put up in a G-Wagon out here
in Highland Park. I'm going to go up to him and
see what this guy did to be able to afford this car
out in Highland Park. I'm going to go up to him and
out in Highland Park in Dallas and see what he
has to say. Excuse me, sir. Quick question for you,
man. Is this your G-Wagon? It is. And what do you
do for living out in Dallas to be able to afford
a G-Wagon? I'm in the insurance business. How long
have you been in the business for? About 15 years.
Among yourself and the most highly successful people
that you study and know, what is that
one trait that they all have in common? They
don't take no for an answer. 90% of people,
when they're told no, they just kind of
say, okay, and they turn away. The successful people,
they find a way to get the
yes. Have you ever been broke before?
Absolutely. At 29, I moved back home.
I didn't have a phone and checking account,
broke. And when you hit rock bottom, there's
only one place to go and that's up.
How old are you now? 48.
If you were to go back in time
and have a conversation with your 20-year-old self,
when you were starting from zero, what's the
best piece of advice that you would give to
your younger self? Stay away from the clubs and
the bottle service and all the money. I went
through that and wasted a lot of money and time
and effort. You're going to have more fun the older
you are having the security and having the
flexibility and freedom to do whatever you want.
Yeah. I had kids later in life and people will
say, oh, you missed out on all that time. And
I said, well, no, but I have
the quality of time, quality versus quantity.
You're in a G-Wagon right now. This is a
lot of people's dream car, people that may be watching,
right? Any advice to someone trying to get
a G-Wagon, man? If you could leave the younger
generation with a couple last piece of advice
on what it really takes to be able to-
Set goals. And I still do it to this day,
the one, three, and five. And when you hit those goals,
that gives you the motivation that helps you
elevate to the next level. So just stay focused,
stay strong, grind it out, man.
You got to grind it out.
I love it, man. That was a great
interview, man. I love your advice. Seriously. Thank you.
That's true, man.
I went into the G-Wagon and my
guy became a multimillionaire in the insurance business.
But what did he say? At 29 years old, dude,
he was broke. He was living at his parents' house
and he had nothing. All he did was he
flipped his mindset, found an industry to become a winner,
and he didn't chase the money. Instead, he
became the best version of himself and became
a multimillionaire, man. Beautiful interview. Shout out
to that man right there. What industry
did you decide to pursue a career in? I had
the blessing to be a former CEO of 7-Eleven. I also
was former chairman and CEO of Blockbuster. I
have done a number of things in retail, technology,
consumer products. I'm working with a couple
of companies in the aerospace industry trying to
build the next Starship. So you were the CEO
of 7-Eleven and Blockbuster? I was the CEO of 7-Eleven
and Blockbuster, yeah. That's incredible. What was
the biggest driving factor of your success
that enabled you to work your way up and
become a CEO of a multi-billion dollar company like 7-Eleven?
Yeah, I've got three things for you. I'll give
them to you. They're my gift. It's these three
things. First, change. People hate change. Everybody
hates change. Harvey McKay, a friend of mine,
author, best-selling author, says the only one that
likes change is a wet baby. And it's true.
People react differently to change and they like go, I
don't want to do this. I don't want to do
this. Well, change is reality and change
equals opportunity. So I've coined that expression. CEO
is all about change equals opportunity. If you embrace
it, you'll see that if I respond to this
change and others don't, I'm going to turn
that into shareholder value. So change can be positive
if you manage it in a positive way. The second
is change. I've been in the business for a long time.
Because when things change, you lack confidence. You're
like, oh no, woe is me. What's going to
happen, right? But confidence is all about
preparation. So the more you prepare, the more
you can win. And the third is about
clarity. Simplicity. The hardest thing in the world is
to keep things simple. So I think it
was Michelangelo or somebody that said true elegance
is in simplicity. And it's so true. If
you can break complex things down into simple solutions,
then it will carry you a
long way. And what many people
lack in the business is confidence. So
I think it's important to have confidence.
And I think that's what's so important in
the corporate world is that clarity of definition.
And clarity comes from both inbound communications,
that means listening well, and outbound communications,
that means keeping things simple when you explain
them. I can't lead if you can't understand.
So it's up to me to keep things simple
and clear. Change, confidence, clarity. You want to know the
path to being a CEO of a company or your
life? It's those three things. Have you ever been broke
before? Oh, I've been broke. I grew up
broke. I grew up without running water. Literally,
in a little shack in Massachusetts. I've
been very broke. We had government surplus cheese,
which I thought was the best cheese in
the world. Those big blocks of cheddar cheese that
mom would bring back. But yeah, I've been broke.
When I first started my career, it was hard to
make bills at the end of the month. It's like,
what doesn't get paid this month? So I know the
feeling. What has been the most amount of
money that you've ever made in a single year?
I can't tell you that. The IRS may be watching.
I've been blessed. I've been really blessed. And
here's how you make money in the corporate world.
It's not salary. A lot of people think, oh,
how much did you make? What's your paycheck? It's
got nothing to do with it. In the corporate world,
it's all about equity. And you get to a certain
point in your career and you get to
participate in the equity programs. Always do that. Always
take advantage of it. I have a friend now
who used to be my administrative assistant. She's at SpaceX
and she couldn't afford the equity that SpaceX was
offering because they have to buy in. I was like,
buy every paycheck.
I'm going to buy every penny that you can of
SpaceX equity because wealth for me didn't occur. I had
trouble making bills on my salary. But when
I finally moved on from 7-Eleven, we sold the
company. I was able to accumulate stock during
that time. And that was the true creation of
wealth. So I recommend that for anyone.
Oh my goodness. That was an amazing interview.
That was seriously great. Seriously.
Thank you. That was awesome.
This video was absolutely insane to
make you guys, but for more content,
like this, we just launched the Hard Knocks
podcast, where we're going to be featuring some
of the biggest business owners in the entire world.
You won't want to miss it. So go subscribe
right now because next week we're going to be
posting a full interview with the former CEO of
7-Eleven and Blockbuster. Hard Knocks podcast. It's going
to be the biggest podcast in the entire
world. Go subscribe right now.